Die Young
压制:随Feng
<font color="#ff8040">Die Young</font>
<font color="#00ffff">活不长</font>
<font color="#ff8040">演唱：Ke$ha</font>
<font color="#00ffff"></font>
<font color="#ff8040">I hear your heart beat to the beat of the drums</font>
<font color="#00ffff">我听到你心跳得和鼓点一样</font>
<font color="#ff8040">Oh what a shame that you came here with someone</font>
<font color="#00ffff">太丢人了吧你还带个人来</font>
<font color="#ff8040">So while you're here in my arms</font>
<font color="#00ffff">就在我抱着你的时候</font>
<font color="#ff8040">Let's make the most of the night like we're gonna die young</font>
<font color="#00ffff">让我们享受这销魂之夜 就像我们知道活不长</font>
<font color="#ff8040">We're gonna die young, we're gonna die young</font>
<font color="#00ffff">我们根本活不长 我们根本活不长</font>
<font color="#ff8040">Let's make the most of the night like we're gonna die young</font>
<font color="#00ffff">让我们享受这销魂之夜 就像我们知道活不长</font>
<font color="#ff8040">Hearts, out of minds</font>
<font color="#00ffff">年轻的心们 疯了</font>
<font color="#ff8040">Running till we out of time</font>
<font color="#00ffff">狂奔的时间 没了</font>
<font color="#ff8040">Wild childs, looking good</font>
<font color="#00ffff">野孩子们 长得漂亮</font>
<font color="#ff8040">Living hard, just like we should</font>
<font color="#00ffff">野蛮生存 本该这样</font>
<font color="#ff8040">Don't care who's watching when we tearing up</font>
<font color="#00ffff">管他谁在看 我们会自顾自哭地狂浪</font>
<font color="#ff8040">You know</font>
<font color="#00ffff">你懂的</font>
<font color="#ff8040">That magic that we got that nobody can touch</font>
<font color="#00ffff">我们之间的魔力他们永远不明白</font>
<font color="#ff8040">You show</font>
<font color="#00ffff">只有你懂的</font>
<font color="#ff8040">Looking for some trouble tonight</font>
<font color="#00ffff">今晚咱来点刺激的</font>
<font color="#ff8040">Take my hand, I'll show you the wild side</font>
<font color="#00ffff">抓住我的手 让你看看姐狂野的一面</font>
<font color="#ff8040">Like it's the last night of our lives</font>
<font color="#00ffff">疯得就像明儿就要死了</font>
<font color="#ff8040">We'll keep dancing 'till we die</font>
<font color="#00ffff">死之前继续狂舞</font>
<font color="#ff8040">I hear your heart beat to the beat of the drums</font>
<font color="#00ffff">我听到你心跳得像鼓点一样</font>
<font color="#ff8040">Oh what a shame that you came here with someone</font>
<font color="#00ffff">太丢人了吧你还带个人来</font>
<font color="#ff8040">So while you're here in my arms</font>
<font color="#00ffff">就在我抱着你的时候</font>
<font color="#ff8040">Let's make the most of the night like we're gonna die young</font>
<font color="#00ffff">就和我一起享受这销魂之夜 就像我们知道活不长</font>
<font color="#ff8040">We're gonna die young, we're gonna die young</font>
<font color="#00ffff">我们根本活不长 我们根本活不长</font>
<font color="#ff8040">Let's make the most of the night like we're gonna die young</font>
<font color="#00ffff">就和我一起享受这销魂之夜 就像我们知道活不长</font>
<font color="#ff8040">Punks, taking shots</font>
<font color="#00ffff">小青年 酒杯都倒过来</font>
<font color="#ff8040">Stripping down to dirty socks</font>
<font color="#00ffff">妹纸们 丝袜都丢上来</font>
<font color="#ff8040">Music up, getting hot</font>
<font color="#00ffff">DJ们 音乐都嗨起来</font>
<font color="#ff8040">Kiss me, give you all you got</font>
<font color="#00ffff">亲吻我 本事都使出来</font>
<font color="#ff8040">It's pretty obvious that you got a crush</font>
<font color="#00ffff">你浑身上下都写着你想要</font>
<font color="#ff8040">You know</font>
<font color="#00ffff">你懂的</font>
<font color="#ff8040">That magic in your pants is making blush</font>
<font color="#00ffff">你牛仔裤里的魔棒让我热血上涌</font>
<font color="#ff8040">You show</font>
<font color="#00ffff">给姐瞧瞧</font>
<font color="#ff8040">Looking for some trouble tonight</font>
<font color="#00ffff">今晚咱来点刺激的</font>
<font color="#ff8040">Take my hand, I'll show you the wild side</font>
<font color="#00ffff">抓住我的手 让你看看姐狂野的一面</font>
<font color="#ff8040">Like it's the last night of our lives</font>
<font color="#00ffff">疯得就像明儿就要死</font>
<font color="#ff8040">We'll keep dancing 'till we die</font>
<font color="#00ffff">死之前继续狂舞</font>
<font color="#ff8040">I hear your heart beat to the beat of the drums</font>
<font color="#00ffff">我听到你心跳得和鼓点一样</font>
<font color="#ff8040">Oh what a shame that you came here with someone</font>
<font color="#00ffff">太丢人了吧你还带个人来</font>
<font color="#ff8040">So while you're here in my arms</font>
<font color="#00ffff">就在我抱着你的时候</font>
<font color="#ff8040">Let's make the most of the night like we're gonna die young</font>
<font color="#00ffff">就和我一起享受这销魂之夜 就像我们知道活不长</font>
<font color="#ff8040">I hear your heart beat to the beat of the drums</font>
<font color="#00ffff">我听到你心跳得和鼓点一样</font>
<font color="#ff8040">Oh what a shame that you came here with someone</font>
<font color="#00ffff">太丢人了吧你还带个人来</font>
<font color="#ff8040">So while you're here in my arms</font>
<font color="#00ffff">就在我抱着你的时候</font>
<font color="#ff8040">Let's make the most of the night like we're gonna die young</font>
<font color="#00ffff">就和我一起享受这销魂之夜 就像我们知道活不长</font>
<font color="#ff8040">We're gonna die young, we're gonna die young</font>
<font color="#00ffff">我们根本活不长 我们根本活不长</font>
压制:随Feng
<font color="#ff8040">Let's make the most of the night like we're gonna die young</font>
<font color="#00ffff">就和我一起享受这销魂之夜 就像我们知道活不长</font>